Hello and welcome.
My name is Abigail Lang and I'm a college
essay coach who got into every college that
I applied to including NYU, Rice, Vanderbilt
with a full ride Cornelius Vanderbilt scholarship,
Georgia Tech and many others and $600,000 in
scholarship offers total.
I have coached over a thousand students now
into getting into their dream schools ranging
from Cornell to Penn to UC Berkeley with the
Regents scholarship to Georgetown, UCLA and
many others and I would love to help you
as well.
Here on my page I offer one-on-one
essay coaching basically meaning that whether
you need help with coming up with ideas for
your essay or having someone help you write
the outline or having someone help you edit,
choose a good topic, revise, give you feedback
I'm here to help with all of that.
So I have either individual sessions you can
do with me if you just want help let's
say getting an idea for your essay, just getting
quick feedback, edits, anything like that to
full packages where I walk you through the
whole process of coming up with your common
app essay or a supplemental package where I
walk you through the process of making all
your supplementals to a package with eight
sessions where I can help you with both your
common app and supplementals.
Whatever it is I'm here to help you.
I can also do scholarship essays.
I can also help with writing the awards or
activities section of your common app.
Whatever it is you may need, whatever you need
help with, I'm happy to help you.
The details are listed on the booking pages
for each of those things.
My goal is just to make the college admissions
process as easy and effective for every student
as it can be because I know personally that
choosing a topic, editing your essay, and everything
that comes with it can be really overwhelming
if you're not sure that you're headed in the
right direction and so since I've reviewed
so many essays and have had such good results
myself it's my goal to give you that information
so that it can simplify the process and you
don't have to do so much guesswork when you're
writing your essays.
Whenever we jump on a call I'll be giving
you the same strategies that I used to get
so many scholarship offers and to get accepted
into every college I applied to because I didn't
even have remarkable stats.
I didn't do more than three extracurriculars
and I didn't win any crazy national awards
but it's really the passion and heart and clarity
and writing style in my essays that helped
me get such good results and I want to
teach you or your student how to do that.
I would love to work with you.
If you have any questions you can email me
at avigallang at gmail.com and I would love
to help you.
Otherwise there's a calendar below where you
can choose the date and time of our call.
If you're buying a package then you go ahead
and choose the date and time of the first
call and you can either email me afterwards
to schedule future calls if you want to go
ahead and do that or while we're actually on
the call I will help you schedule the next
one or the remaining ones if you'd like to.
I'd love to work with you and it was
so nice to meet you.